<?xml-stylesheet href="/rss.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>@ly-nld&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.lgbt.sh/</link>
    <description>Recent content on @ly-nld&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Mikka 2023 - 2023</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 12:22:37 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://blog.lgbt.sh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Harmony Within Us Development Update</title>
        <link>https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/halted-development/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 12:22:37 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/halted-development/</guid>
        <description>@ly-nld&#39;s blog https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/halted-development/ -&lt;p&gt;Hey HWU community,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope this post finds you well. I wanted to provide a quick update on the development of Harmony Within Us (HWU). As many of you know, our shared journey toward creating a supportive and inclusive space is incredibly important to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to a heightened focus on my mental health and overall well-being, I&amp;rsquo;ve made the decision to temporarily pause the development of HWU. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial for me to take this time to ensure that I can continue to contribute positively to our community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to reassure you that this pause is not a goodbye or an end. It&amp;rsquo;s a necessary step to prioritize self-care, and I believe it will ultimately lead to a more robust and impactful HWU in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I understand that many of you are excited about the project, and I truly appreciate your support and enthusiasm. Please don&amp;rsquo;t worry – Harmony Within Us is still very much alive, and I am committed to returning to development as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your understanding and continued support. Let&amp;rsquo;s keep fostering harmony within ourselves and our community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more updates, and take care. &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
- https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/halted-development/ - Mikka 2023 - 2023</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Gender Dysphoria Rant</title>
        <link>https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/mtf-issue-rant/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 14:51:33 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/mtf-issue-rant/</guid>
        <description>@ly-nld&#39;s blog https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/mtf-issue-rant/ -&lt;p&gt;So, here&amp;rsquo;s the deal. I never signed up for this whole MtF, gender dysphoria package. Like, seriously, who would willingly choose this rollercoaster of emotions? Not me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s rewind a bit.&lt;/em&gt; Imagine waking up one day and realizing your gender compass is pointing in the opposite direction. It&amp;rsquo;s like, &amp;ldquo;Hello dysphoria, my old friend. Can we not do this today?&amp;rdquo; But nope, life had other plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And here&amp;rsquo;s the kicker.&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s not a phase, it&amp;rsquo;s not a choice. It&amp;rsquo;s just me, dealing with this hand I&amp;rsquo;ve been dealt. I didn&amp;rsquo;t wake up one morning and think, &amp;ldquo;You know what would be fun? Let&amp;rsquo;s switch genders and see how that goes.&amp;rdquo; Nope, not a thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about societal expectations.&lt;/em&gt; I mean, come on. Why can&amp;rsquo;t we all just be who we are without the constant judgment and raised eyebrows? It&amp;rsquo;s exhausting. If got a euro every time someone said; &amp;ldquo;But why would you choose this?&amp;rdquo; I would be a millionaire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you ever wonder why I didn&amp;rsquo;t choose an &amp;rsquo;easier&amp;rsquo; path, well, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t an option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sorry, rant over. Thank you for reading.&lt;/p&gt;
- https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/mtf-issue-rant/ - Mikka 2023 - 2023</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>The Privacy Perils of Discord: A Closer Look</title>
        <link>https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/discord-privacy/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:27:13 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/discord-privacy/</guid>
        <description>@ly-nld&#39;s blog https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/discord-privacy/ -&lt;p&gt;In the past 7 years, &lt;strong&gt;Discord&lt;/strong&gt; has emerged as a popular platform for communication, particularly within gaming communities and social circles. However, beneath its user-friendly interface lies a complex web of privacy concerns that users should be aware of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;discords-privacy-policy-a-critical-examination&#34;&gt;Discord&amp;rsquo;s Privacy Policy: A Critical Examination&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discord&amp;rsquo;s Privacy Policy&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;https://discordapp.com/privacy&#34;&gt;Discord Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;) outlines the platform&amp;rsquo;s practices regarding user data. While the document is comprehensive, the devil often lies in the details. People should pay attention to data collection, storage, and sharing policies to understand the extent of their digital footprint on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;government-requests-and-user-privacy&#34;&gt;Government Requests and User Privacy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discussions on Reddit (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/80l8se/discord_receives_government_requests_no_plans_on/&#34;&gt;Reddit Post&lt;/a&gt;) have shed light on &lt;strong&gt;Discord&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/strong&gt; stance when faced with government requests for user data. Users express concern towards the platform&amp;rsquo;s apparent lack of commitment to protecting user privacy in such situations. This raises questions about the balance between user rights and legal obligations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;terms-of-service-what-users-should-know&#34;&gt;Terms of Service: What Users Should Know&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Terms of Service; Didn&amp;rsquo;t Read&lt;/em&gt; (TOS;DR) offers a summarization of &lt;strong&gt;Discord&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/strong&gt; Terms of Service (&lt;a href=&#34;https://tosdr.org/en/service/536&#34;&gt;TOS;DR - Discord&lt;/a&gt;). This website breaks down the legal jargon and highlights key points, making it easier for people to comprehend the implications of agreeing to &lt;strong&gt;Discord&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/strong&gt; terms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;third-party-observations&#34;&gt;Third-Party Observations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an era of digital transparency, independent observers and critics play a crucial role in scrutinizing online platforms. A critical article on Spyware (&lt;a href=&#34;https://spyware.neocities.org/articles/discord&#34;&gt;Spyware Article&lt;/a&gt;) provides a thought-provoking examination of &lt;strong&gt;Discord&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/strong&gt; privacy-related issues.&lt;/p&gt;
- https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/discord-privacy/ - Mikka 2023 - 2023</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>The Impact of Political Stances on the Transgender Community in the Netherlands</title>
        <link>https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/lgbt-concern-nl/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:11:30 +0100</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/lgbt-concern-nl/</guid>
        <description>@ly-nld&#39;s blog https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/lgbt-concern-nl/ -&lt;p&gt;In recent times, the rights and well-being of the LGBTQ+ community, especially transgender individuals, have become a focal point of political discourse in the Netherlands. Unfortunately, some political parties, like the Forum for Democracy (FvD), have been criticized for their stance on LGBTQ+ rights, contributing to an environment that can be harmful to the transgender community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;unraveling-the-fvds-impact&#34;&gt;Unraveling the FvD&amp;rsquo;s Impact&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Forum for Democracy, through its policies and public statements, has raised concerns about its support for the rights and dignity of transgender individuals. This party&amp;rsquo;s positions, often rooted in traditionalist ideologies, can be detrimental to the progress made in securing equal rights for the LGBTQ+ community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;propaganda-and-misrepresentation&#34;&gt;Propaganda and Misrepresentation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is vital to address how political propaganda and nit-picking tactics are applied to cast transgender individuals in a negative light. By highlighting isolated incidents and promoting a skewed narrative, certain political entities contribute to the harmful stereotypes and biases of LGBTQ+ individuals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-call-to-action&#34;&gt;A Call to Action&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the face of such challenges, it becomes imperative for the LGBTQ+ community and its allies to be informed and engaged. Platforms like RainbowVote (&lt;a href=&#34;https://rainbowvote.nu/&#34;&gt;rainbowvote.nu&lt;/a&gt;) play a vital role in empowering individuals with the knowledge needed to make informed decisions during the elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;exposing-anti-lgbtq-propaganda&#34;&gt;Exposing Anti-LGBTQ+ Propaganda&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recent incidents, such as this FvD advertisement &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/LHBTI/comments/17tg4zm&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, have come under scrutiny for promoting anti-LGBTQ+ sentiments. This Reddit post highlights the importance of vigilance and the need to counteract misleading narratives that can adversely affect the transgender community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is crucial to stand against policies and propaganda that undermine the rights and well-being of transgender individuals. Only together we can strive towards a more accepting and supportive society.&lt;/p&gt;
- https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/lgbt-concern-nl/ - Mikka 2023 - 2023</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>これはテストです</title>
        <link>https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/pr-test-001/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/pr-test-001/</guid>
        <description>@ly-nld&#39;s blog https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/pr-test-001/ -&lt;p&gt;Test&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;おやすみ&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://github.com/ly-nld/blog/assets/38471793/2fddb79c-2d7d-4982-b93a-da1f35e49589&#34; alt=&#34;hat&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
- https://blog.lgbt.sh/posts/pr-test-001/ - Mikka 2023 - 2023</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss> 